Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
here?
ここ?
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいいの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
wait a minute...
ちょっと待って...
It's soaked. Is it soaked?
びしょびしょだ びしょびしょ いっちゃったの?
Do you want me to do it for you?
せいざしてもらう?
It may be cold though
冷たいかもしれないけど
Hey, what's wrong?
ち っちゃいどうしたの?
cormorant
う
- It feels so good and soft
ーん めっちゃ気持ちいい 柔らかい
Do you really want to do this to your teacher?
先生 にやってあげたいの マジ?
Hello, are you drooling?
こんにちさん ヨダレ垂らしてくるの?
amazing
すごい
Hey, you can do it amazingly.
ね すごいできるんだね
Power is coming out
力 が出てる
What happened?
い っちゃったの?
I went crazy
い っちゃ った
of?
の?
What happened to your whole body?
全 身どうしたの?
Do you want me to say it?
言ってほしい?
Is this no good?
これじゃダメ?
No, why?
ダメ なんで?
No good
ダメ
It feels good like this, right?
こんな もん気持ちいいでしょ
Well then, there are various things.
ちょっと じゃあ いろんなさ
Can you put your feet up?
足 立ててくの?
Would you like to put your foot in it once?
一回足入れしてくの?
Awesome, can you touch the one that came out?
すごい 出たやつちょっと触ってくの?
Was it serious?
マジかった?
good
よかった